http://www.livingstonparishnews.com/site/privacy.html

This Week's Ads
How can I advertise?
Try our app!
This Week's Ads
How can I advertise?
Try our app!
Home
The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways we treat personal information about you and your computer, mobile or other device when you access, visit and/or use the Service. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere.The Service generally collects personal information with your specific knowledge and consent. For instance, when you subscribe to our publication(s), register for certain services, or register and/or set up an account/profile to access the Service, you may be provided, or required to choose, a password and/or User ID, and you may provide a credit, debit, or charge card number, or other payment information, as well as your name, telephone number, email and/or street address, and other personal information. Information such as your age, gender, an avatar, and the number for your mobile or other device may also be requested. All such information shall be referred to in this Privacy Policy as your "Registration Information".Our servers may also automatically collect information about you, your online behavior and your computer, mobile or other device.If you choose to access, visit and/or use any third party social networking service that may be integrated with the Service, we may receive personal information about you and your computer, mobile or other device that you have made available to those services, including information about your contacts on those services. Your decision to use a social networking service in connection with our Service is voluntary. However, you should make sure you are comfortable with the information your third party social networking services may make available to our Service by visiting those services' privacy policies and/or modifying your privacy settings directly with those services. We reserve the right to use, transfer, assign, sell, share, and provide access to all personal information about you and your computer, mobile or other device that we receive through third-party social networking services in the same ways described in this Agreement as all of your other information.We use personal information you supply through the Service to provide you with the merchandise, product, service, and/or Content you have requested. For example, if you subscribe to any of our publications, we may use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice and your mailing address to send you the publication. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, and/or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs.Unless otherwise specified on the Service, we may sell or share information about you and your computer, mobile or other device, including without limitation your Registration Information and other personal information, with our parent, subsidiaries, and affiliates and with carefully selected companies who we think may offer services and/or products that may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to have your personal information shared with unaffiliated third parties, contact our Privacy Policy Coordinator as described at the end of this document. If you do not wish to receive future commercial messages from us, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions contained within the message you receive. (But note that you may continue to receive certain communications from us, such as transactional or relationship messages, and/or messages about your account/profile).We may also allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance, market research, community and forums management, and auction services, but only to the extent necessary to provide those services. And if you choose to purchase merchandise, products and/or services, including without limitation Content, on or through features on the Service, we may forward your information to third parties for services such as credit card or other payment processing. There are also times when you provide information about yourself to us in areas of the Service that may be managed or participated in by third parties. In such cases, the information may be used by us and by such third parties, each pursuant to its own policies. We may also provide your information to our advertisers, so that they can serve ads to you that meet your needs or match your interests. While we may seek to require such third parties to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, we do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties.We may provide access to our database in order to cooperate with official investigations or legal proceedings initiated by governmental and/or law enforcement officials, as well as private parties, including, for example, in response to subpoenas, or other legal process.We reserve the right to use the information we collect about your computer, mobile or other device which may at times be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose. Geographic location information about you and/or your computer, mobile or other device may specifically be used to show you content and sponsored messaging based on geographic location.We reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any lawful business purpose.In addition, as our business changes, we may buy or sell various assets. In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by us, our parent or any subsidiary or affiliated entity are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another company, the information about our Service users may be among the transferred assets.We reserve the right to identify you from your Registration Information and/or to merge or co-mingle anonymous or non-personally identifiable data about you, your offline and online behavior, and/or your computer, mobile or other device (including its geographic location), with your Registration Information and/or other personally identifiable data for any lawful business purpose.The Service may place and/or store code or other types of information and/or devices (e.g., "cookies") on your computer, mobile or other device ("Local Device Storage"). We may use Local Device Storage for any lawful business purpose. For example, if you register on any part of the Service and are given the option to save your user name and password, we may provide this convenience to you via Local Device Storage. Local Device Storage may also collect and store your personally identifiable information, which may be shared with our parent, subsidiaries, and affiliates and other companies.If you do not want Local Device Storage, your computer, mobile or other device may include an option that allows you to not accept it. However, if you disable Local Device Storage, some portions of the Service may not function properly.In addition to Local Device Storage, we may use web beacons, web bugs, clear gifs, and similar technologies (collectively, together with Local Device Storage, the "Tracking Technologies"). Our advertising service vendors and other third parties may also use Tracking Technologies to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this Service and other sites, applications, destinations, and services you have visited, and to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements, and for other lawful business purposes. In doing so, these third parties may collect non-personally identifiable data. The use of Tracking Technologies by third parties is subject to their own privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy, and we have no responsibility or liability in connection therewith.Your information may be transferred to, and maintained on, servers and databases located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as your jurisdiction. Please be advised that we may transfer your information to and from any state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction, and process it in the United States or elsewhere. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to any such transfer.Because no data transmission is completely secure, we cannot guarantee the security of the information you send to us or the security of our servers, networks or databases, and by using the Service you agree to assume all risk in connection with the information sent to us or collected by us when you use the Service, and we are not responsible for any loss of such information or the consequences thereof.If you elect to store information, such as your personal information or other Registration Information, where others may access it, we are not responsible for any loss of such information or the consequences thereof. If you lose a computer, mobile or other device, or it is stolen, that contains your personal information or other Registration Information, it is up to you to take all the steps necessary to protect yourself.In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you. If notification is appropriate, we may notify you via your computer, mobile or other device.This Service is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to register for the Service or provide any personal information or use the Service in any way. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17, inclusive, must get the permission of their parents or legal guardians before making purchases, including subscriptions, on this Service.If your children disclose information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of the Service, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so.If you're worried about your children's activities or their privacy on the Service, contact our Privacy Policy Coordinator as described below.If you have any concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, please feel free to contact our Privacy Policy Coordinator as follows:Privacy Policy CoordinatorThe Livingston Parish NewsPO Box 1529Denham Springs LA 70727-1529editor@lpn1898.comNote: Only inquiries about this policy or your personal information should be sent to the Privacy Policy Coordinator. No other communications will be accepted or responded to.For communications on other matters, please contact us through the means described on the Service.3rd Party AdvertisingThe Service may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website. These companies may use information (not including any Personally-Identifying Information) about your visits to the Website and other websites that are contained in Web Cookies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Using a tool created by the Network Advertising Initiative, you can opt out of several third-party ad servers' and networks' Web Cookies simultaneously. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please complete the following links:   http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp,   http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/, or http://www.aboutads.info/choices/. Please contact us if you would like to know the identity of the third-party advertising companies we are currently using to serve ads.The Service may allow advertisers to choose the characteristics of users who will see their advertisements, and we may use any of the Non-Personally Identifying Information we have collected (including information you may have decided not to show to other users, such as your birth year or other sensitive personal information or preferences) to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements. We do not identify you to the advertiser.If you don't agree to the terms contained in this User Agreement and Privacy Policy, you must immediately exit the Service.
Most Popular
Articles
Videos
Audio
Collections
Commented
ArticlesDenham Springs PD investigating inappropriate relationship at Denham High School between former teacher, studentLouisiana State Police: Unrestrained driver dies in single-vehicle crash in MaurepasFOOTBALL | Janis stepping down as Albany football coachMaurepas School secretary retires after 44 years of serviceHometown hero: Learn about Miller Xavier Aydell, the Livingston Parish native who died in the attack on Pearl Harbor 79 years agoNo one injured in Friday morning fire in Walker; cause ‘likely’ a space heaterLivingston Parish schools superintendent tests positive for COVID-19, is ‘successfully managing’ symptoms at homeAmite River Christmas on the Bayou hosting Christmas boat parade Dec. 5Meal fundraiser for ‘selfless’ volunteer in critical condition following accident taking place in Denham Springs Dec. 5COVID-19 testing site to run in Denham Springs Dec. 8
Videos
AudioSorry, there are no recent results for popular audio clips.
CollectionsGIRLS BASKETBALL | Springfield at Albany | Photo GalleryGIRLS BASKETBALL | Fontainebleau at Denham Springs | Photo GalleryGIRLS BASKETBALL | Live Oak at Springfield | Photo GallerySoutheastern Louisiana University celebrates fall 2020 graduates | Photo GalleryGIRLS BASKETBALL | Independence at Springfield | Photo GalleryBOYS BASKETBALL | French Settlement at Maurepas | Photo GalleryGIRLS BASKETBALL | Springfield at Pine | Photo GalleryGIRLS BASKETBALL | French Settlement at Maurepas | Photo GalleryDenham Springs High theatre to perform ‘It’s a Wonderful Life’ radio play | Photo GalleryFOOTBALL | Live Oak at Haughton | Photo Gallery
CommentedGov. Edwards warns of ‘horrendous results’ if holiday celebrations aren’t altered amid COVID-19 (2)OPINION | Two Georgia seats wouldn't help Democrats much (2)Forbes names Livingston Parish school system second-best company to work for in Louisiana in 2020 (1)OPINION | More than 145 million reasons to demand transparency (1)Louisiana going to ‘revised Phase Two’ order as COVID-19 cases, hospitalizations surge, Gov. Edwards announces (1)OPINION | After mail-in election, Biden must deliver on postal reform (1)Louisiana State Police: Unrestrained driver dies in single-vehicle crash in Maurepas (1)
Around the Web
Did you know that you can travel to Angola with an eVisa?
Updated
Oct 18, 2019
(Editor's Note: The following is a paid story for iVisa)
Is sushi healthy?
Infectious Diseases: Common cold or the flu?
To view our latest e-Edition click the image on the left.
Katherine Renee Leonard-Dupre, born January 24, 1962, was a mo…
Dr. James C. Rippel
Updated
12 hrs ago
Dr. James C. Rippel, 87, passed away peacefully, surrounded by…
Click here for more Obituaries -->
© Copyright 2020 The Livingston Parish News, 688 Hatchell Lane Denham Springs, LA | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
